<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MobiSquid</string>
    <string name="number">Phone number</string>
    <string name="passphoto">
<![CDATA[
The processing of your account application may be delayed if you do not submit a photo that meets the requirements below.  To avoid processing delays, we recommend you that if you take the photo yourself with a smartphone camera, the digital image must adhere to the following specifications:<br>the subject should be evenly lit, taken against a plain background, without any harsh shadows or reflections on glasses,<br>·the subject should have a blank expression (no smiling, for example) and they should be face-on to the camera.<br><br>If taken from your gallery or computer, photos must not be digitally enhanced or altered to change your appearance in any way.<br>
]]>
</string>
    <string name="idphoto">
<![CDATA[
The processing of your account application may be delayed if you do not submit a photo that meets the requirements below.  To avoid processing delays, we recommend you that if you take the photo yourself with a smartphone camera, the digital image must adhere to the following specifications:<br>the subject should be evenly lit, taken against a plain background, without any harsh shadows or reflections on glass.Take full surface of your identity card.
]]>
</string>
    <string name="proof_residence">
<![CDATA[
The processing of your account application may be delayed if you do not submit a photo that meets the requirements below.  To avoid processing delays, we recommend you that if you take the photo yourself with a smartphone camera, the digital image must adhere to the following specifications:<br>the subject should be evenly lit, taken against a plain background, without any harsh shadows or reflections on glass.Make sure that alleast you capture the stamp and signtures on the paper.<br>
]]>
</string>
    <string name="note">Please note that for security purposes this device is not registered to carry out financial services. Please answer the questions below to switch your account to this device.</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="id_number">ID number</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="nice_html">
<![CDATA[
<p><b> MCASH ACCOUNT TERMS AND CONDITIONS.</b></p>

<b>1.Agreement and Acceptance</b>

<br>This agreement becomes effective between you and Housing Finance Bank Ltd (“the bank’, ‘we” or “us”) at the time of registering for Mcash Bank
account or at the time you access the Mcash product, whichever occurs first.<br>
<br><b>Definitions:</b><br>
<b>2.“Alerts”</b> mean the customized messages sent as IVR (as defined herein) to the Customer over mobile phones.
<br><b>3.“MCash Account”</b> shall mean an electronic account opened for a customer upon enrolment for the MCash solution at locations approved by
Housing Finance Bank,
<br><b>4.“Customer”</b> means a person who enrols for the m-cash solution and has accepted these Terms & Conditions.
<br><b>5.“Instructions”</b> shall mean the instructions given to Housing Finance Bank directly or through Agents/aggregators by the Customer through IVR in
relation to the MCash Account.
<br><b>6.“Partners “ </b>shall mean establishments, wherever located, which accept payment under the Mcash solution including but not limited to stores,
shops, restaurants, hotels, airline organizations, websites, mail order advertisers (whether retailers, distributors or manufacturers), mail order outlets
(whether wholesalers, retailers, distributors or manufacturers) advertised as accepting payment on the Mcash Payment Platform.
<br><b>7.“IVR”</b> shall mean Interactive Voice Response,
<br><b>8.“Terms & Conditions” </b>means these Terms & Conditions including any amendments all annexure, schedules, incorporated by reference from time
to time.
<br><b>9.“Services” </b>shall mean the products offered by Housing Finance Bank through the m-cash payment solution.
<br><b>10.“Valid Card”</b> shall mean an unexpir<br>
<br><b>Terms and conditions</b>
<br><b>11.Charges:</b> Charges shall accrue on the m-cash account whenever a customer transacts on the Mcash payment Platform.
<br><b>12.Lodging in Complaints:</b> All complaints about the MCash payment solution shall be reported to the Bank or its Agents as soon as possible for
attention. The Bank shall upon receipt of any complaint, give feed back to the customer within reasonable time depending on the nature of the
complaint.
<br><b>13.Freezing of Accounts:</b> The bank may at any time freeze any account of the customer if there are reasons to believe the MCash account is being used for
fraudulent/money laundering activities whether those activities be proved or not.
<br><b>14.Pass Code Protection and Irregularities:</b> A “Pass code” refers to your PIN (Personal Identification Number). You must protect and keep your PIN and/
or access codes confidential at all times. Please note that it is not safe to store it on your computer. You must report any compromise of your PIN or Pass
codes to the Bank without delay. You may do this by contacting our Customer Service Centre. Once you notify us to disable your PIN or access code, we
are entitled to:
<br>&nbsp</item>a) Reject all instructions received after such notification;
<br>&nbsp</item>b) Suspend the processing of all instructions not yet executed;
<br>&nbsp</item>c) Reverse (if possible) all executed transactions with effect from such date and time as we may reasonably determine the unauthorized use to have
commenced;
<br>&nbsp</item>d) Deactivate the pass code without further notice;
Please note that your PIN/Pass code shall be confidential and there will never be a reason for any person including a member of our staff at Customer
Service Centre to know or ask for your PIN or Pass code. Do not disclose your Pass code to these persons, regardless of whether you called them or they
called you.

<br><b>15.Interpretation:</b> In these Terms and Conditions the expression, ‘the customer’ shall include any person or persons, firm or corporate body and the
word “’his “also refers to the female gender.
<br><b>16.Amendments: </b>Any addition or alteration of these Terms and Conditions made from time to time by the Bank of which has been given to the
Account Holder shall be binding upon the Account Holder as fully as if the same were contained in these Terms and Conditions.
<br><b>17.Your Authority:</b> Whenever a customer’s PIN or pass code is entered onto the Mcash payment platform, it shall be deemed as full authority by the
customer to the Bank to carry any instructions flowing there from.
<br><b>18.Limits:</b> Housing Finance Bank reserves the right to set transaction limits, the amount and frequency of Payments that a Customer may make on
the MCash payment platform, without prejudice to the generality of the aforesaid, processing of all the Instructions is subject to the availability of
free, clear and available funds/limits in the Customer’s m-cash account or Valid Card. In the event of clear funds/limits not being available, Housing
Finance Bank shall not process the Instructions and shall not make Payments. The Customer understands that Housing Finance Bank shall not be
liable for any late charges, penalty, loss, damage, expenses, whether direct or indirect, incurred/to be incurred by the Customer in this regard and/
or the Utilities/Services not being delivered to the Customer by the agents on account of failure to execute Instructions and the Customer hereby
agrees not to hold Housing Finance Bank liable in this regard.
<br><b>19.Indemnity: </b>In consideration of Housing Finance Bank agreeing to provide to the Customer the MCash Account, the Customer hereby irrevocably agrees
to indemnify and keep Housing Finance Bank indemnified, at all times from all losses, damage, costs, legal fees, charges and expenses and consequences
whatsoever, suffered or incurred by Housing Finance Bank on account of any claims, actions, suits or otherwise instituted by the Customer, or any third party
whatsoever, arising out of or in connection with the use of the MCash Account and any transactions initiated by the use of the MCash Account, whether
with or without the knowledge of the Customer, or whether the same have been initiated bona fide or otherwise which transactions, the Customer hereby
acknowledges, Housing Finance Bank has processed on the Instructions and authority of the Customer in accordance with these Terms & Conditions.
<br><b>20.Unavailability of MCash solution:</b> We will at all times and for whatever reason, have the sole and exclusive right to suspend or terminate
the Mcash solution without any prior notification or giving any reasons for such termination or suspension, especially where the Bank finds it
appropriate to do so or as by may be required by law to take such action. The customer acknowledges and accepts that the Mcash payment
platform may be unavailable from time to time for any reason, including:
<br>&nbsp</item>a)technical failure or problems with the communication system itself or our communication system underlying banking systems (the bank
system);
<br>&nbsp</item>b)technical failure or problems with a communication system directly or indirectly underlying Mcash payment plat form that is owned or
controlled by other persons (third party system);
<br>&nbsp</item>c)Unavailability or telecommunication or electricity services; or other circumstances beyond our control.
<br>&nbsp</item>d)You undertake in the event of unavailability of Mcash payment platform, to mitigate your potential losses by using any other means of
communication with us for the duration of the unavailability of banking-cash payment platform.
<br>&nbsp</item>e)any interruption, malfunction, downtime or other failure of services provided by third parties, including, without limitation, third party
systems such as the public switched telecommunication service providers, internet service providers, electricity suppliers, local authorities
and certification authorities;
<br>&nbsp</item>f)Any event over which we have no direct control.<br>
<br><b>NOTE:</b> The customer hereby acknowledges that the Bank shall not be liable for any loss arising out of general interruptions with the Internet System
since the Mcash payment Platform is an internet based payment solution.
<br><b>21.Disclosure of customer account information</b><br>
The Bank may disclose details of and relating to the customer’s Account to any credit reference, Agency or other like institutions as it deems
necessary or as permitted by the Law.
]]>
</string>
    <string-array name="CountryCodes">
        <item>93,AF</item>
        <item>355,AL</item>
        <item>213,DZ</item>
        <item>376,AD</item>
        <item>244,AO</item>
        <item>672,AQ</item>
        <item>54,AR</item>
        <item>374,AM</item>
        <item>297,AW</item>
        <item>61,AU</item>
        <item>43,AT</item>
        <item>994,AZ</item>
        <item>973,BH</item>
        <item>880,BD</item>
        <item>375,BY</item>
        <item>32,BE</item>
        <item>501,BZ</item>
        <item>229,BJ</item>
        <item>975,BT</item>
        <item>591,BO</item>
        <item>387,BA</item>
        <item>267,BW</item>
        <item>55,BR</item>
        <item>673,BN</item>
        <item>359,BG</item>
        <item>226,BF</item>
        <item>95,MM</item>
        <item>257,BI</item>
        <item>855,KH</item>
        <item>237,CM</item>
        <item>1,CA</item>
        <item>238,CV</item>
        <item>236,CF</item>
        <item>235,TD</item>
        <item>56,CL</item>
        <item>86,CN</item>
        <item>61,CX</item>
        <item>61,CC</item>
        <item>57,CO</item>
        <item>269,KM</item>
        <item>242,CG</item>
        <item>243,CD</item>
        <item>682,CK</item>
        <item>506,CR</item>
        <item>385,HR</item>
        <item>53,CU</item>
        <item>357,CY</item>
        <item>420,CZ</item>
        <item>45,DK</item>
        <item>253,DJ</item>
        <item>670,TL</item>
        <item>593,EC</item>
        <item>20,EG</item>
        <item>503,SV</item>
        <item>240,GQ</item>
        <item>291,ER</item>
        <item>372,EE</item>
        <item>251,ET</item>
        <item>500,FK</item>
        <item>298,FO</item>
        <item>679,FJ</item>
        <item>358,FI</item>
        <item>33,FR</item>
        <item>689,PF</item>
        <item>241,GA</item>
        <item>220,GM</item>
        <item>995,GE</item>
        <item>49,DE</item>
        <item>233,GH</item>
        <item>350,GI</item>
        <item>30,GR</item>
        <item>299,GL</item>
        <item>502,GT</item>
        <item>224,GN</item>
        <item>245,GW</item>
        <item>592,GY</item>
        <item>509,HT</item>
        <item>504,HN</item>
        <item>852,HK</item>
        <item>36,HU</item>
        <item>91,IN</item>
        <item>62,ID</item>
        <item>98,IR</item>
        <item>964,IQ</item>
        <item>353,IE</item>
        <item>44,IM</item>
        <item>972,IL</item>
        <item>39,IT</item>
        <item>225,CI</item>
        <item>81,JP</item>
        <item>962,JO</item>
        <item>7,KZ</item>
        <item>254,KE</item>
        <item>686,KI</item>
        <item>965,KW</item>
        <item>996,KG</item>
        <item>856,LA</item>
        <item>371,LV</item>
        <item>961,LB</item>
        <item>266,LS</item>
        <item>231,LR</item>
        <item>218,LY</item>
        <item>423,LI</item>
        <item>370,LT</item>
        <item>352,LU</item>
        <item>853,MO</item>
        <item>389,MK</item>
        <item>261,MG</item>
        <item>265,MW</item>
        <item>60,MY</item>
        <item>960,MV</item>
        <item>223,ML</item>
        <item>356,MT</item>
        <item>692,MH</item>
        <item>222,MR</item>
        <item>230,MU</item>
        <item>262,YT</item>
        <item>52,MX</item>
        <item>691,FM</item>
        <item>373,MD</item>
        <item>377,MC</item>
        <item>976,MN</item>
        <item>382,ME</item>
        <item>212,MA</item>
        <item>258,MZ</item>
        <item>264,NA</item>
        <item>674,NR</item>
        <item>977,NP</item>
        <item>31,NL</item>
        <item>599,AN</item>
        <item>687,NC</item>
        <item>64,NZ</item>
        <item>505,NI</item>
        <item>227,NE</item>
        <item>234,NG</item>
        <item>683,NU</item>
        <item>850,KP</item>
        <item>47,NO</item>
        <item>968,OM</item>
        <item>92,PK</item>
        <item>680,PW</item>
        <item>507,PA</item>
        <item>675,PG</item>
        <item>595,PY</item>
        <item>51,PE</item>
        <item>63,PH</item>
        <item>870,PN</item>
        <item>48,PL</item>
        <item>351,PT</item>
        <item>1,PR</item>
        <item>974,QA</item>
        <item>40,RO</item>
        <item>7,RU</item>
        <item>250,RW</item>
        <item>590,BL</item>
        <item>685,WS</item>
        <item>378,SM</item>
        <item>239,ST</item>
        <item>966,SA</item>
        <item>221,SN</item>
        <item>381,RS</item>
        <item>248,SC</item>
        <item>232,SL</item>
        <item>65,SG</item>
        <item>421,SK</item>
        <item>386,SI</item>
        <item>677,SB</item>
        <item>252,SO</item>
        <item>27,ZA</item>
        <item>82,KR</item>
        <item>34,ES</item>
        <item>94,LK</item>
        <item>290,SH</item>
        <item>508,PM</item>
        <item>249,SD</item>
        <item>597,SR</item>
        <item>268,SZ</item>
        <item>46,SE</item>
        <item>41,CH</item>
        <item>963,SY</item>
        <item>886,TW</item>
        <item>992,TJ</item>
        <item>255,TZ</item>
        <item>66,TH</item>
        <item>228,TG</item>
        <item>690,TK</item>
        <item>676,TO</item>
        <item>216,TN</item>
        <item>90,TR</item>
        <item>993,TM</item>
        <item>688,TV</item>
        <item>971,AE</item>
        <item>256,UG</item>
        <item>44,GB</item>
        <item>380,UA</item>
        <item>598,UY</item>
        <item>1,US</item>
        <item>998,UZ</item>
        <item>678,VU</item>
        <item>39,VA</item>
        <item>58,VE</item>
        <item>84,VN</item>
        <item>681,WF</item>
        <item>967,YE</item>
        <item>260,ZM</item>
        <item>263,ZW</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_main_screen">MainScreen</string>
    <string name="qrtime">Qrcode</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="reason">Reason/Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">RegistrationActivity</string>
    <string name="help_support">Support/Help</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_setting">SettingActivity</string>
    <string name="termcondition"><![CDATA[Settings T & C]]></string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="tag_content">content</string>
    <string name="tag_menu">menu</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat_main">Chat</string>
    <string name="accept_terms"><![CDATA[By clicking register, you accept T&C]]></string>
    <array name="menuOptions">
        <item>Chat</item>
        <item>Broadcast</item>
        <item>Invite</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Groups</item>

    </array>
    <string name="title_activity_mainmenu">Mainmenu</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="title_activity_eshopping">EshoppingActivity</string>

    <!-- ecom stuff-->
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ph_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="ecommerce">E-Commerce</string>
    <string name="message_fetching_data">Fetching data for categories</string>
    <string name="addtocart">Add To Cart</string>
    <string name="infoadd">+ info</string>
    <string name="infominus">- info</string>
    <string name="productid" formatted="false">Product ID : %d</string>
    <string name="description" formatted="false">Description : %s</string>
    <string name="color" formatted="false">Color : %s</string>
    <string name="price" formatted="false">Price : %.2f</string>
    <string name="total">Total:</string>
    <string name="pleaseadd">Please add items to basket.</string>
    <string name="sharemessage">Join now http://support.mobisquid.com</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="server_not_available">Could not connect to server</string>
    <string name="not_found">URL not found</string>
    <string name="internal_server_error">Internal Server Error</string>
    <string name="title_activity_support">Support</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="waiting">All our agents are currently occupied. Your views are important to us, please wait for the next available agent.</string>
</resources>
